JHOSEHP RENDON

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Tech Lover, Hustler, Constant
Learner. Always looking for
opportunities where software can
solve real problems.

CONTACT

+ 57 3142289827

Cr. 7h 151-56 Bogotá, Colombia

jhosehp.rendon@gmail.com

SUMMARY

4 years experience in the technology field as an entrepreneur, startup founder and freelancer. Worked for various IT projects as Frontend developer and product leader.

His enthusiasm for code comes down to a passion for taking great ideas and bringing them to life.

Experienced with React-Redux framework and a solid knowledge of JavaScript ES6 / ES7, HTML, CSS, SASS.

Additional experience developing mobile Apps for iOS and Android with React Native.

SKILLS

Frontend: JavaScript ES6 / ES7, HTML, CSS, SASS, React, Redux, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Material UI, React Native and testing with Jest, Mocha.

Tools: Git, Github, Heroku, Jira, Storybook.

Design: Illustrator, Photoshop, Sketch, Adobe XD, InVision.

Methodologies: Agile - SCRUM, Sprint Design Process,

User Centric Design.

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native speaker

English - Conversational | Advanced

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer at Upwork

Frontend Developer | April 2017 - Present

Working for a software agency that helps their clients develop better interfaces and make new apps that help them meet their business goals.

In charge of developing the admin app and client onboarding process for a fleet management company and a business loan startup.

Technology used: React, Redux, HTML, CSS, JS(ES6, ES7) Git, Jest, REST API, Storybook, Adobe XD.

Sohamfit

CEO Co-Founder | January 2014 - October 2016

Sohamfit was a project in the fitness industry. The web app was built to bring a digital platform for fitness enthusiasts and people that wanted to exercise at home.

Doing design and frontend web development.

Technology used: HTML, CSS, JS(ES6, ES7), Illustrator, Photoshop.

Huespedcanino

CEO Co-Founder | July 2014 - March 2016

Huespedcanino was aimed to become the Airbnb for pets in Latin America. Backed and funded by Wayra a Telefonica Startup Accelerator.

In charge of product/Business development, growth hacking and web development.

Technology used: HTML, CSS, JS(ES6, ES7), Illustrator, Photoshop.

Tipket Ltd

CEO Co-Founder | August 2013 - July 2014

Tipket was a startup backed by Entrepreneurial Spark, an Accelerator from the UK. It was a mobile app for geotargeting products in physical stores.

In charge of design process, product/Business development, growth hacking and web development.

Technology used: HTML, CSS, JS(ES6, ES7), Illustrator, Photoshop.

Vopak

Management Trainee | January 2010 - July 2010

Vopak is a chemical storage and handling company based in the Netherlands with operations across the globe.

In charge of implementing new processes and applying innovation in operations. Trained for management positions.

EDUCATION

BS Mechanical Engineer

Universidad Central de Venezuela January 2005 – June 2010

MSc Global Innovation Management

University of Strathclyde – Technische Universitat Hamburg January 2011 – June 2013

COURSES

Node with React: Fullstack: udemy.com 2018

React Native - Advanced: udemy.com 2018

The Complete Course React Native: udemy.com 2018

Web UI with Adobe XD: udemy.com 2018

Mobile App Design with Sketch: udemy.com 2018

Illustrator CC 2019 Master Class: udemy.com 2018

React – The Complete Guide: udemy.com 2017

Modern React with Redux: udemy.com 2017

The Complete JS Course: udemy.com 2016

REFERENCES

Leonardo Gedler:

Email: leonardogedler@gmail.com

Orlando Arzola:

Email: orlandoarzola86@gmail.com